,Reference,Index,Token,Start_pos,BIO_Flair,Precision_Flair,BIO_Flair-large,Precision_Flair-large,BIO_Flair_Splitter,Precision_Flair_Splitter,BIO_spaCy-md,BIO_spaCy-trf
0,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,0,§,0,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,1,4.1.1,2,O,-,O,-,O,-,B-CARDINAL,B-CARDINAL
2,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,2,EPIRUS,9,O,-,B-LOC,0.9999366998672485,B-LOC,0.9999462366104126,B-ORG,O
3,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,3,:,15,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
4,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,4,The,17,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
5,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,5,third,21,O,-,O,-,O,-,B-ORDINAL,B-ORDINAL
6,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,6,great,27,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
7,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,7,Gulf,33,B-MISC,0.6030405958493551,O,-,O,-,B-LOC,B-LOC
8,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,8,of,38,I-MISC,0.6030405958493551,O,-,O,-,I-LOC,O
9,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,9,Europe,41,I-MISC,0.6030405958493551,B-LOC,0.9999897480010986,B-LOC,0.9999909400939941,I-LOC,B-LOC
10,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,10,begins,48,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
11,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,11,at,55,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
12,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,12,the,58,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
13,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,13,mountains,62,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
14,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,14,of,72,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
15,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,15,Acroceraunia,75,B-LOC,0.9949479103088379,B-LOC,0.9999752044677734,B-LOC,0.9999786615371704,B-GPE,B-LOC
16,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,16,",",87,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
17,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,17,and,89,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
18,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,18,ends,93,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
19,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,19,at,98,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
20,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,20,the,101,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
21,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,21,Hellespont,105,B-LOC,0.9734165668487549,B-LOC,0.9999699592590332,B-LOC,0.9999749660491943,B-GPE,B-LOC
22,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,22,",",115,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
23,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,23,embracing,117,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
24,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,24,an,127,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
25,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,25,extent,130,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
26,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,26,of,137,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
27,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,27,2500,140,O,-,O,-,O,-,B-QUANTITY,B-QUANTITY
28,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,28,miles,145,O,-,O,-,O,-,I-QUANTITY,I-QUANTITY
29,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,29,",",150,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
30,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,30,exclusive,152,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
31,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,31,of,162,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
32,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,32,the,165,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
33,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,33,sea-line,169,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
34,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,34,of,178,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
35,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,35,nineteen,181,O,-,O,-,O,-,B-CARDINAL,B-CARDINAL
36,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,36,smaller,190,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
37,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,37,gulfs,198,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
38,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,38,.,203,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
92,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,92,All,444,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
93,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,93,the,448,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
94,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,94,fabulous,452,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
95,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,95,lore,461,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
96,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,96,of,466,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
97,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,97,Greece,469,B-LOC,0.9996402263641357,B-LOC,0.9999760389328003,B-LOC,0.9999628067016602,B-GPE,B-GPE
98,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,98,",",475,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
99,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,99,as,477,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
100,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,100,well,480,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
101,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,101,as,485,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
102,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,102,the,488,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
103,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,103,effulgence,492,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
104,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,104,of,503,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
105,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,105,her,506,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
106,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,106,literature,510,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
107,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,107,",",520,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
108,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,108,first,522,O,-,O,-,O,-,B-ORDINAL,O
109,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,109,shone,528,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
110,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,110,forth,534,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
111,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,111,upon,540,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
112,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,112,the,545,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
113,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,113,banks,549,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
114,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,114,of,555,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
115,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,115,this,558,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
116,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,116,Gulf,563,B-LOC,0.997848629951477,O,-,B-LOC,0.9991594552993774,B-LOC,B-LOC
117,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,117,.,567,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
118,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,118,We,569,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
119,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,119,shall,572,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
120,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,120,therefore,578,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
121,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,121,dwell,588,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
122,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,122,a,594,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
123,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,123,little,596,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
124,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,124,the,603,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
125,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,125,longer,607,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
126,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,126,upon,614,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
127,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,127,it,619,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
128,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.1,128,.,621,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
129,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,0,§,0,O,-,O,-,O,-,B-PERSON,O
130,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,1,4.1.2,2,O,-,O,-,O,-,I-PERSON,B-CARDINAL
131,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,2,Epirus,9,B-LOC,0.8068370223045349,B-LOC,0.9999581575393677,B-LOC,0.9999737739562988,I-PERSON,B-GPE
132,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,3,",",15,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
133,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,4,generally,17,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
134,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,5,so,27,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
135,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,6,called,30,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
136,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,7,",",36,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
137,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,8,begins,38,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
138,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,9,at,45,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
139,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,10,the,48,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
140,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,11,mountains,52,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
141,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,12,of,62,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
142,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,13,Acroceraunia,65,B-LOC,0.9966726303100586,B-LOC,0.9999778270721436,B-LOC,0.9999825954437256,B-GPE,B-LOC
143,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,14,.,77,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
144,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,15,The,79,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
145,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,16,first,83,O,-,O,-,O,-,B-ORDINAL,O
146,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,17,people,89,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
147,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,18,that,96,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
148,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,19,we,101,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
149,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,20,meet,104,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
150,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,21,are,109,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
151,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,22,the,113,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
152,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,23,Chaones,117,B-MISC,0.8914539217948914,B-MISC,0.9999862909317017,B-MISC,0.9999855756759644,B-ORG,B-NORP
153,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,24,",",124,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
154,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,25,from,126,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
155,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,26,whom,131,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
156,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,27,Chaonia,136,B-LOC,0.5481219291687012,B-LOC,0.9999794960021973,B-LOC,0.9999803304672241,B-PERSON,B-GPE
157,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,28,receives,144,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
158,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,29,its,153,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
159,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,30,name,157,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
160,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,31,",",161,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
161,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,32,then,163,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
162,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,33,the,168,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
163,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,34,Thesproti,172,B-MISC,0.9738898277282715,B-MISC,0.9999842643737793,B-MISC,0.999982476234436,B-PERSON,B-NORP
164,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,35,",",181,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
165,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,36,and,183,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
166,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,37,then,187,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
167,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,38,the,192,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
168,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,39,Antigonenses,196,B-MISC,0.9947794675827026,B-MISC,0.9999829530715942,B-MISC,0.9999822378158569,B-PERSON,B-NORP
169,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,40,.,208,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
170,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,41,We,210,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
171,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,42,then,213,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
172,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,43,come,218,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
173,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,44,to,223,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
174,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,45,the,226,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
175,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,46,place,230,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
176,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,47,where,236,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
177,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,48,Aornos,242,B-PER,0.5864120721817017,B-PER,0.7487255334854126,B-PER,0.748719334602356,B-PERSON,B-PERSON
178,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,49,stood,249,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
179,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,50,",",254,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
180,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,51,with,256,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
181,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,52,its,261,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
182,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,53,exhalations,265,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
183,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,54,so,277,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
184,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,55,deadly,280,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
185,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,56,to,287,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
186,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,57,the,290,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
187,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,58,feathered,294,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
188,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,59,race,304,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
189,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,60,",",308,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
190,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,61,the,310,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
191,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,62,Cestrinis,314,B-MISC,0.9779428839683533,B-MISC,0.9999351501464844,B-MISC,0.9999351501464844,B-PRODUCT,B-NORP
192,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,63,",",323,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
193,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,64,the,325,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
194,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,65,Perrhaebi,329,B-MISC,0.9582797884941101,B-MISC,0.999945878982544,B-MISC,0.999945878982544,B-PERSON,B-NORP
195,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,66,",",338,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
196,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,67,in,340,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
197,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,68,whose,343,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
198,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,69,country,349,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
199,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,70,Mount,357,B-LOC,0.9270880818367004,B-LOC,0.9999553561210632,B-LOC,0.9999553561210632,B-NORP,B-LOC
200,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,71,Pindus,363,I-LOC,0.9270880818367004,I-LOC,0.9999553561210632,I-LOC,0.9999553561210632,I-NORP,I-LOC
201,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,72,is,370,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
202,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,73,situate,373,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
203,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,74,",",380,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
204,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,75,the,382,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
205,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,76,Cassiopaei,386,B-MISC,0.9210910201072693,B-MISC,0.9998700618743896,B-MISC,0.9998700618743896,B-PRODUCT,B-NORP
206,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,77,",",396,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
207,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,78,the,398,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
208,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,79,Dryopes,402,B-MISC,0.9177334904670715,B-MISC,0.9999121427536011,B-MISC,0.9999121427536011,B-GPE,B-NORP
209,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,80,",",409,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
210,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,81,the,411,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
211,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,82,Sellae,415,B-MISC,0.8621249794960022,B-MISC,0.9998779296875,B-MISC,0.9998779296875,O,B-NORP
212,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,83,",",421,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
213,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,84,the,423,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
214,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,85,Hellopes,427,B-MISC,0.9045764803886414,B-MISC,0.9998983144760132,B-MISC,0.9998983144760132,B-GPE,B-NORP
215,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,86,",",435,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
216,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,87,the,437,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
217,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,88,Molossi,441,B-MISC,0.9623256325721741,B-MISC,0.9998509883880615,B-MISC,0.9998509883880615,B-PERSON,B-NORP
218,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,89,",",448,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
219,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,90,in,450,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
220,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,91,whose,453,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
221,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,92,territory,459,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
222,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,93,is,469,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
223,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,94,the,472,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
224,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,95,temple,476,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
225,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,96,of,483,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
226,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,97,the,486,O,-,O,-,O,-,B-LOC,O
227,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,98,Dodonaean,490,B-LOC,0.7957488000392914,B-MISC,0.9999749660491943,B-MISC,0.9999749660491943,I-LOC,B-NORP
228,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,99,Jupiter,500,I-LOC,0.7957488000392914,B-PER,0.9998960494995117,B-PER,0.9998960494995117,I-LOC,B-LOC
229,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,100,",",507,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
230,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,101,so,509,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
231,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,102,famous,512,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
232,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,103,for,519,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
233,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,104,its,523,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
234,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,105,oracle,527,O,-,O,-,O,-,B-ORG,O
235,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,106,;,533,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
236,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,107,and,535,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
237,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,108,Mount,539,B-LOC,0.8729001581668854,B-LOC,0.9997686743736267,B-LOC,0.9997686743736267,B-PERSON,B-LOC
238,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,109,Tomarus,545,I-LOC,0.8729001581668854,I-LOC,0.9997686743736267,I-LOC,0.9997686743736267,I-PERSON,I-LOC
239,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,110,",",552,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
240,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,111,so,554,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
241,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,112,highly,557,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
242,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,113,praised,564,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
243,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,114,by,572,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
244,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,115,Theopompus,575,B-PER,0.7950180172920227,B-PER,0.9998830556869507,B-PER,0.9998830556869507,B-ORG,B-PERSON
245,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,116,",",585,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
246,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,117,with,587,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
247,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,118,its,592,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
248,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,119,hundred,596,O,-,O,-,O,-,B-CARDINAL,B-CARDINAL
249,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,120,springs,604,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
250,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,121,gushing,612,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
251,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,122,from,620,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
252,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,123,its,625,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
253,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,124,foot,629,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
254,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.2,125,.,633,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
255,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,0,§,0,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
256,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,1,4.1.3,2,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,B-CARDINAL
257,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,2,Epirus,9,B-LOC,0.6686323881149292,B-LOC,0.9999825954437256,B-LOC,0.9999816417694092,B-GPE,B-GPE
258,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,3,",",15,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
259,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,4,properly,17,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
260,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,5,so,26,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
261,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,6,called,29,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
262,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,7,",",35,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
263,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,8,advances,37,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
264,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,9,towards,46,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
265,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,10,Magnesia,54,B-LOC,0.9713950157165527,B-LOC,0.9999899864196777,B-LOC,0.9999885559082031,B-GPE,B-GPE
266,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,11,and,63,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
267,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,12,Macedonia,67,B-LOC,0.9999337196350098,B-LOC,0.9999942779541016,B-LOC,0.9999940395355225,B-GPE,B-GPE
268,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,13,",",76,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
269,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,14,having,78,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
270,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,15,at,85,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
271,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,16,its,88,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
272,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,17,back,92,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
273,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,18,the,97,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
274,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,19,Dassaretae,101,B-MISC,0.5571772456169128,B-MISC,0.9996389150619507,B-MISC,0.9995025396347046,B-ORG,B-NORP
275,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,20,",",111,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
276,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,21,previously,113,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
277,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,22,mentioned,124,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
278,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,23,",",133,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
279,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,24,a,135,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
280,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,25,free,137,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
281,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,26,nation,142,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
282,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,27,",",148,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
283,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,28,and,150,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
284,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,29,after,154,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
285,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,30,them,160,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
286,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,31,the,165,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
287,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,32,Dardani,169,B-MISC,0.6552766561508179,B-MISC,0.9999544620513916,B-MISC,0.9999440908432007,B-GPE,B-NORP
288,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,33,",",176,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
289,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,34,a,178,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
290,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,35,savage,180,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
291,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,36,race,187,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
292,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,37,.,191,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
293,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,38,On,193,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
294,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,39,the,196,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
295,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,40,left,200,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
296,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,41,hand,205,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
297,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,42,",",209,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
298,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,43,before,211,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
299,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,44,the,218,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
300,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,45,Dardani,222,B-LOC,0.5756378173828125,B-MISC,0.9998570680618286,B-MISC,0.9998570680618286,B-GPE,B-NORP
301,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,46,are,230,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
302,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,47,extended,234,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
303,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,48,the,243,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
304,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,49,Triballi,247,B-MISC,0.7593342065811157,B-MISC,0.999889612197876,B-MISC,0.999889612197876,B-PRODUCT,B-NORP
305,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,50,and,256,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
306,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,51,the,260,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
307,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,52,nations,264,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
308,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,53,of,272,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
309,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,54,Moesia,275,B-LOC,0.9989476799964905,B-LOC,0.9999861717224121,B-LOC,0.9999861717224121,B-GPE,B-GPE
310,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,55,",",281,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
311,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,56,while,283,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
312,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,57,in,289,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
313,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,58,front,292,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
314,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,59,of,298,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
315,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,60,them,301,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
316,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,61,the,306,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
317,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,62,Medi,310,B-LOC,0.49320927262306213,B-MISC,0.9999845027923584,B-MISC,0.9999845027923584,B-ORG,B-NORP
318,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,63,and,315,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
319,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,64,the,319,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
320,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,65,Denselatae,323,B-MISC,0.9645297527313232,B-MISC,0.9999775886535645,B-MISC,0.9999775886535645,B-ORG,B-NORP
321,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,66,join,334,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
322,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,67,",",338,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
323,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,68,and,340,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
324,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,69,next,344,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
325,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,70,to,349,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
326,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,71,them,352,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
327,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,72,the,357,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
328,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,73,Thracians,361,B-MISC,0.9871456623077393,B-MISC,0.9999880790710449,B-MISC,0.9999880790710449,B-NORP,B-NORP
329,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,74,",",370,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
330,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,75,who,372,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
331,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,76,stretch,376,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
332,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,77,away,384,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
333,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,78,as,389,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
334,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,79,far,392,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
335,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,80,as,396,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
336,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,81,the,399,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
337,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,82,Euxine,403,B-MISC,0.8933195471763611,B-LOC,0.9996771812438965,B-LOC,0.9996771812438965,B-PERSON,B-LOC
338,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,83,:,409,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
339,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,84,in,411,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
340,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,85,such,414,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
341,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,86,a,419,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
342,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,87,manner,421,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
343,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,88,is,428,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
344,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,89,a,431,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
345,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,90,rampart,433,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
346,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,91,raised,441,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
347,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,92,around,448,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
348,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,93,the,455,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
349,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,94,lofty,459,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
350,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,95,heights,465,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
351,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,96,of,473,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
352,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,97,Rhodope,476,B-LOC,0.9993878602981567,B-LOC,0.9999136924743652,B-LOC,0.9999136924743652,B-LOC,B-LOC
353,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,98,",",483,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
354,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,99,and,485,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
355,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,100,then,489,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
356,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,101,of,494,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
357,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,102,Haemus,497,B-LOC,0.5688583850860596,B-LOC,0.9999544620513916,B-LOC,0.9999544620513916,B-ORG,B-GPE
358,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.3,103,.,503,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
359,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,0,§,0,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
360,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,1,4.1.4,2,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
361,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,2,On,9,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
362,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,3,the,12,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
363,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,4,coast,16,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
364,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,5,of,22,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
365,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,6,Epirus,25,B-LOC,0.9987334609031677,B-LOC,0.9999918937683105,B-LOC,0.9999920129776001,B-GPE,B-GPE
366,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,7,is,32,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
367,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,8,the,35,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
368,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,9,fortress,39,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
369,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,10,of,48,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
370,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,11,Chimaer,51,B-LOC,0.9965512752532959,B-LOC,0.9999861717224121,B-LOC,0.9999864101409912,B-GPE,B-GPE
371,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,12,",",58,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
372,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,13,situate,60,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
373,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,14,upon,68,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
374,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,15,the,73,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
375,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,16,Acroceraunian,77,B-LOC,0.7804837822914124,B-MISC,0.9996200799942017,B-MISC,0.9994887113571167,B-NORP,B-NORP
376,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,17,range,91,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
377,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,18,",",96,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
378,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,19,and,98,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
379,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,20,below,102,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
380,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,21,it,108,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
381,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,22,the,111,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
382,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,23,spring,115,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
383,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,24,known,122,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
384,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,25,as,128,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
385,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,26,the,131,O,-,O,-,O,-,B-PRODUCT,B-LOC
386,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,27,Royal,135,B-LOC,0.9405175745487213,B-LOC,0.6619165241718292,B-LOC,0.6788703203201294,I-PRODUCT,I-LOC
387,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,28,Waters,141,I-LOC,0.9405175745487213,I-LOC,0.6619165241718292,I-LOC,0.6788703203201294,I-PRODUCT,I-LOC
388,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,29,;,147,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
389,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,30,then,149,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
390,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,31,the,154,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
391,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,32,towns,158,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
392,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,33,of,164,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
393,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,34,Maeandria,167,B-LOC,0.9917516112327576,B-LOC,0.9999592304229736,B-LOC,0.9999592304229736,B-GPE,B-GPE
394,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,35,",",176,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
395,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,36,and,178,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
396,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,37,Cestria,182,B-LOC,0.780210018157959,B-LOC,0.9999632835388184,B-LOC,0.9999624490737915,B-PERSON,B-GPE
397,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,38,",",189,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
398,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,39,the,191,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
399,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,40,Thyamis,195,B-MISC,0.6396070122718811,B-LOC,0.9998194575309753,B-LOC,0.9997850060462952,B-ORG,B-LOC
400,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,41,",",202,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
401,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,42,a,204,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
402,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,43,river,206,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
403,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,44,of,212,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
404,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,45,Thesprotia,215,B-LOC,0.9722641706466675,B-LOC,0.9998981952667236,B-LOC,0.9998612403869629,B-GPE,B-GPE
405,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,46,",",225,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
406,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,47,the,227,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
407,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,48,colony,231,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
408,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,49,of,238,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
409,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,50,Buthrotum,241,B-LOC,0.9557929635047913,B-LOC,0.9998509883880615,B-LOC,0.9997928738594055,B-GPE,B-GPE
410,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,51,",",250,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
411,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,52,and,252,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
412,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,53,the,256,O,-,O,-,O,-,B-LOC,B-LOC
413,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,54,Ambracian,260,B-LOC,0.9249127805233002,B-LOC,0.9999785423278809,B-LOC,0.9999789595603943,I-LOC,I-LOC
414,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,55,Gulf,270,I-LOC,0.9249127805233002,I-LOC,0.9999785423278809,I-LOC,0.9999789595603943,I-LOC,I-LOC
415,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,56,",",274,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
416,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,57,so,276,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
417,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,58,famed,279,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
418,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,59,in,285,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
419,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,60,history,288,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
420,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,61,;,295,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
421,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,62,which,297,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
422,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,63,",",302,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
423,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,64,with,304,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
424,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,65,an,309,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
425,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,66,inlet,312,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
426,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,67,only,318,O,-,O,-,O,-,B-QUANTITY,B-QUANTITY
427,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,68,half,323,O,-,O,-,O,-,I-QUANTITY,I-QUANTITY
428,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,69,a,328,O,-,O,-,O,-,I-QUANTITY,I-QUANTITY
429,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,70,mile,330,O,-,O,-,O,-,I-QUANTITY,I-QUANTITY
430,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,71,in,335,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
431,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,72,width,338,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
432,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,73,",",343,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
433,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,74,receives,345,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
434,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,75,a,354,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
435,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,76,vast,356,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
436,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,77,body,361,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
437,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,78,of,366,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
438,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,79,water,369,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
439,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,80,from,375,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
440,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,81,the,380,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
441,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,82,sea,384,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
442,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,83,",",387,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
443,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,84,being,389,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
444,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,85,thirty-seven,395,O,-,O,-,O,-,B-QUANTITY,B-QUANTITY
445,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,86,miles,408,O,-,O,-,O,-,I-QUANTITY,I-QUANTITY
446,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,87,in,414,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
447,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,88,length,417,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
448,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,89,",",423,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
449,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,90,and,425,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
450,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,91,fifteen,429,O,-,O,-,O,-,B-CARDINAL,B-CARDINAL
451,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,92,in,437,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
452,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,93,width,440,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
453,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,94,.,445,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
454,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,95,The,447,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
455,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,96,river,451,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
456,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,97,Acheron,457,B-LOC,0.7443466186523438,B-LOC,0.9996591806411743,B-LOC,0.999852180480957,B-ORG,B-LOC
457,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,98,",",464,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
458,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,99,which,466,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
459,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,100,runs,472,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
460,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,101,through,477,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
461,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,102,Acherusia,485,B-LOC,0.9972234964370728,B-LOC,0.99998939037323,B-LOC,0.9999921321868896,B-FAC,B-LOC
462,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,103,",",494,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
463,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,104,a,496,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
464,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,105,lake,498,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
465,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,106,of,503,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
466,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,107,Thesprotia,506,B-LOC,0.996810257434845,B-LOC,0.9999619722366333,B-LOC,0.9999856948852539,B-GPE,B-GPE
467,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,108,",",516,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
468,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,109,flows,518,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
469,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,110,into,524,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
470,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,111,it,529,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
471,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,112,after,532,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
472,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,113,a,538,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
473,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,114,course,540,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
474,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,115,of,547,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
475,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,116,thirty-six,550,O,-,O,-,O,-,B-QUANTITY,B-QUANTITY
476,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,117,miles,561,O,-,O,-,O,-,I-QUANTITY,I-QUANTITY
477,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,118,;,566,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
478,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,119,it,568,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
479,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,120,is,571,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
480,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,121,considered,574,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
481,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,122,wonderful,585,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
482,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,123,for,595,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
483,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,124,its,599,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
484,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,125,bridge,603,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
485,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,126,",",609,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
486,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,127,1000,611,O,-,O,-,O,-,B-QUANTITY,B-QUANTITY
487,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,128,feet,616,O,-,O,-,O,-,I-QUANTITY,I-QUANTITY
488,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,129,in,621,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
489,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,130,length,624,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
490,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,131,",",630,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
491,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,132,by,632,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
492,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,133,a,635,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
493,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,134,people,637,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
494,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,135,who,644,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
495,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,136,look,648,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
496,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,137,upon,653,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
497,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,138,everything,658,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
498,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,139,as,669,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
499,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,140,wonderful,672,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
500,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,141,that,682,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
501,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,142,belongs,687,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
502,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,143,to,695,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
503,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,144,themselves,698,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
504,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,145,.,708,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
505,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,146,Upon,710,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
506,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,147,this,715,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
507,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,148,Gulf,720,B-LOC,0.9883068203926086,B-LOC,0.9991666078567505,B-LOC,0.999903678894043,B-LOC,B-LOC
508,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,149,is,725,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
509,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,150,also,728,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
510,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,151,situate,733,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
511,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,152,the,741,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
512,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,153,town,745,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
513,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,154,of,750,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
514,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,155,Ambracia,753,B-LOC,0.9900876879692078,B-LOC,0.9999916553497314,B-LOC,0.9999915361404419,B-ORG,B-GPE
515,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,156,.,761,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
516,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,157,There,763,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
517,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,158,are,769,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
518,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,159,also,773,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
519,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,160,the,778,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
520,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,161,Aphas,782,B-MISC,0.5442123413085938,B-LOC,0.9990198612213135,B-LOC,0.9994000196456909,B-PERSON,B-LOC
521,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,162,and,788,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
522,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,163,the,792,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
523,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,164,Arachthus,796,B-MISC,0.5317201614379883,B-LOC,0.999416708946228,B-LOC,0.9995508790016174,B-ORG,B-LOC
524,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,165,",",805,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
525,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,166,rivers,807,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
526,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,167,of,814,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
527,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,168,the,817,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
528,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,169,Molossi,821,B-LOC,0.7555109858512878,B-MISC,0.9431877136230469,B-MISC,0.9723053574562073,B-PERSON,B-LOC
529,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,170,;,828,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
530,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,171,the,830,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
531,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,172,city,834,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
532,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,173,of,839,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
533,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,174,Anactoria,842,B-LOC,0.9967106580734253,B-LOC,0.999971866607666,B-LOC,0.9999902248382568,B-PERSON,B-GPE
534,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,175,",",851,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
535,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,176,and,853,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
536,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,177,the,857,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
537,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,178,place,861,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
538,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,179,where,867,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
539,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,180,Pandosia,873,B-PER,0.7949461340904236,B-LOC,0.9999603033065796,B-LOC,0.9999889135360718,B-FAC,B-GPE
540,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,181,stood,882,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
541,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.1.4,182,.,887,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
542,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,0,§,0,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
543,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,1,4.2.1,2,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,B-CARDINAL
544,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,2,ACARNANIA,9,O,-,B-LOC,0.9999837875366211,B-LOC,0.9999877214431763,B-ORG,B-GPE
545,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,3,:,18,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
546,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,4,The,20,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
547,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,5,towns,24,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
548,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,6,of,30,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
549,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,7,Acarnania,33,B-LOC,0.9992990493774414,B-LOC,0.9999833106994629,B-LOC,0.9999853372573853,B-GPE,B-GPE
550,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,8,",",42,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
551,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,9,the,44,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
552,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,10,ancient,48,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
553,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,11,name,56,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
554,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,12,of,61,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
555,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,13,which,64,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
556,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,14,was,70,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
557,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,15,Curetis,74,B-MISC,0.8956925868988037,B-LOC,0.999936580657959,B-LOC,0.9999392032623291,B-ORG,B-GPE
558,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,16,",",81,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
559,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,17,are,83,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
560,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,18,Heraclia,87,B-LOC,0.8643442392349243,B-LOC,0.9999673366546631,B-LOC,0.9999701976776123,B-PERSON,B-GPE
561,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,19,",",95,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
562,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,20,Echinus,97,B-LOC,0.5332009792327881,B-LOC,0.9999696016311646,B-LOC,0.9999727010726929,B-LOC,B-GPE
563,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,21,",",104,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
564,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,22,and,106,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
565,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,23,",",109,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
566,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,24,on,111,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
567,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,25,the,114,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
568,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,26,coast,118,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
569,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,27,",",123,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
570,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,28,Actium,125,B-LOC,0.6976045966148376,B-LOC,0.9999581575393677,B-LOC,0.9999651908874512,B-ORG,B-GPE
571,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,29,",",131,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
572,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,30,a,133,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
573,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,31,colony,135,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
574,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,32,founded,142,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
575,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,33,by,150,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
576,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,34,Augustus,153,B-PER,0.9510497450828552,B-PER,0.9999325275421143,B-PER,0.9999436140060425,B-PERSON,B-PERSON
577,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,35,",",161,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
578,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,36,with,163,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
579,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,37,its,168,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
580,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,38,famous,172,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
581,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,39,temple,179,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
582,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,40,of,186,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
583,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,41,Apollo,189,B-LOC,0.5144025087356567,B-PER,0.999875545501709,B-PER,0.9999043941497803,B-ORG,B-PERSON
584,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,42,and,196,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
585,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,43,the,200,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
586,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,44,free,204,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
587,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,45,city,209,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
588,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,46,of,214,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
589,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,47,Nicopolis,217,B-LOC,0.9985232949256897,B-LOC,0.9999778270721436,B-LOC,0.9999799728393555,B-GPE,B-GPE
590,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,48,.,226,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
591,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,49,Passing,228,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
592,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,50,out,236,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
593,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,51,of,240,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
594,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,52,the,243,O,-,O,-,O,-,B-LOC,B-LOC
595,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,53,Ambracian,247,B-LOC,0.9931898415088654,B-LOC,0.9999821782112122,B-LOC,0.9999839663505554,I-LOC,I-LOC
596,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,54,Gulf,257,I-LOC,0.9931898415088654,I-LOC,0.9999821782112122,I-LOC,0.9999839663505554,I-LOC,I-LOC
597,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,55,into,262,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
598,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,56,the,267,O,-,O,-,O,-,B-LOC,B-LOC
599,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,57,Ionian,271,B-LOC,0.969662070274353,B-LOC,0.999983012676239,B-LOC,0.9999847412109375,I-LOC,I-LOC
600,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,58,Sea,278,I-LOC,0.969662070274353,I-LOC,0.999983012676239,I-LOC,0.9999847412109375,I-LOC,I-LOC
601,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,59,",",281,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
602,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,60,we,283,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
603,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,61,come,286,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
604,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,62,to,291,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
605,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,63,the,294,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
606,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,64,coast,298,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
607,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,65,of,304,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
608,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,66,Leucadia,307,B-LOC,0.9885457158088684,B-LOC,0.9999904632568359,B-LOC,0.9999909400939941,B-GPE,B-GPE
609,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,67,",",315,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
610,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,68,with,317,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
611,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,69,the,322,O,-,O,-,O,-,B-ORG,B-FAC
612,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,70,Promontory,326,B-LOC,0.5446568032105764,B-LOC,0.9999618927637736,B-LOC,0.9999630451202393,I-ORG,I-FAC
613,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,71,of,337,I-LOC,0.5446568032105764,I-LOC,0.9999618927637736,I-LOC,0.9999630451202393,I-ORG,I-FAC
614,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,72,Leucate,340,I-LOC,0.5446568032105764,I-LOC,0.9999618927637736,I-LOC,0.9999630451202393,I-ORG,I-FAC
615,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,73,",",347,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
616,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,74,and,349,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
617,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,75,then,353,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
618,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,76,the,358,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
619,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,77,Gulf,362,B-LOC,0.9736912250518799,B-LOC,0.9999924898147583,B-LOC,0.9999927282333374,B-LOC,B-LOC
620,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,78,and,367,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
621,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,79,the,371,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
622,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,80,peninsula,375,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
623,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,81,of,385,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
624,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,82,Leucadia,388,B-LOC,0.9914159178733826,B-LOC,0.9999884366989136,B-LOC,0.9999903440475464,B-GPE,B-LOC
625,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,83,",",396,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
626,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,84,which,398,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
627,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,85,last,404,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
628,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,86,was,409,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
629,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,87,formerly,413,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
630,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,88,called,422,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
631,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,89,Neritis,429,B-MISC,0.8238857984542847,B-LOC,0.9999690055847168,B-LOC,0.9999759197235107,B-PRODUCT,B-LOC
632,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,90,.,436,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
633,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,91,By,438,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
634,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,92,the,441,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
635,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,93,exertions,445,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
636,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,94,of,455,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
637,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,95,the,458,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
638,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,96,inhabitants,462,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
639,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,97,it,474,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
640,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,98,was,477,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
641,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,99,once,481,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
642,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,100,cut,486,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
643,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,101,off,490,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
644,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,102,from,494,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
645,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,103,the,499,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
646,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,104,mainland,503,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
647,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,105,",",511,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
648,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,106,but,513,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
649,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,107,was,517,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
650,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,108,again,521,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
651,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,109,joined,527,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
652,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,110,to,534,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
653,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,111,it,537,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
654,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,112,by,540,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
655,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,113,the,543,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
656,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,114,vast,547,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
657,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,115,bodies,552,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
658,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,116,of,559,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
659,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,117,sand,562,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
660,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,118,accumulated,567,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
661,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,119,through,579,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
662,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,120,the,587,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
663,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,121,action,591,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
664,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,122,of,598,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
665,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,123,the,601,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
666,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,124,winds,605,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
667,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,125,.,610,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
668,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,126,This,612,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
669,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,127,spot,617,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
670,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,128,is,622,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
671,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,129,called,625,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
672,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,130,Dioryctos,632,B-MISC,0.9791959524154663,B-LOC,0.9999784231185913,B-LOC,0.9999876022338867,B-ORG,B-GPE
673,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,131,",",641,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
674,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,132,and,643,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
675,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,133,is,647,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
676,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,134,three,650,O,-,O,-,O,-,B-CARDINAL,B-QUANTITY
677,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,135,stadia,656,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,I-QUANTITY
678,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,136,in,663,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
679,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,137,length,666,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
680,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,138,:,672,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
681,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,139,on,674,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
682,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,140,the,677,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
683,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,141,peninsula,681,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
684,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,142,is,691,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
685,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,143,the,694,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
686,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,144,town,698,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
687,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,145,of,703,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
688,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,146,Leucas,706,B-LOC,0.9956489205360413,B-LOC,0.9999858140945435,B-LOC,0.9999896287918091,B-PERSON,B-GPE
689,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,147,",",712,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
690,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,148,formerly,714,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
691,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,149,called,723,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
692,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,150,Neritus,730,B-MISC,0.7852404713630676,B-LOC,0.9999761581420898,B-LOC,0.9999793767929077,B-ORG,B-GPE
693,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,151,.,737,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
694,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,152,We,739,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
695,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,153,next,742,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
696,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,154,come,747,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
697,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,155,to,752,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
698,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,156,Alyzia,755,B-LOC,0.966779887676239,B-LOC,0.9999779462814331,B-LOC,0.9999850988388062,B-GPE,B-GPE
699,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,157,",",761,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
700,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,158,Stratos,763,B-LOC,0.6309454441070557,B-LOC,0.9999507665634155,B-LOC,0.9999746084213257,B-GPE,B-GPE
701,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,159,",",770,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
702,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,160,and,772,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
703,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,161,Argos,776,B-LOC,0.8136256337165833,B-LOC,0.9999656677246094,B-LOC,0.9999845027923584,B-ORG,B-GPE
704,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,162,",",781,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
705,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,163,surnamed,783,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
706,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,164,Amphilochian,792,B-MISC,0.7638669610023499,B-MISC,0.9999648332595825,B-MISC,0.9999866485595703,B-NORP,B-NORP
707,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,165,",",804,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
708,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,166,cities,806,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
709,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,167,of,813,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
710,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,168,the,816,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
711,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,169,Acarnanians,820,B-MISC,0.9379903674125671,B-MISC,0.9999872446060181,B-MISC,0.9999908208847046,B-NORP,B-NORP
712,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,170,:,831,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
713,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,171,the,833,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
714,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,172,river,837,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
715,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,173,Achelous,843,O,-,B-LOC,0.9955657124519348,B-LOC,0.9981328845024109,O,B-LOC
716,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,174,flows,852,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
717,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,175,from,858,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
718,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,176,the,863,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
719,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,177,heights,867,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
720,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,178,of,875,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
721,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,179,Pindus,878,B-LOC,0.8471336364746094,B-LOC,0.999964714050293,B-LOC,0.9999884366989136,B-NORP,B-GPE
722,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,180,",",884,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
723,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,181,and,886,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
724,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,182,",",889,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
725,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,183,after,891,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
726,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,184,separating,897,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
727,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,185,Acarnania,908,B-MISC,0.5650107860565186,B-LOC,0.9999908208847046,B-LOC,0.9999936819076538,B-GPE,B-GPE
728,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,186,from,918,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
729,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,187,Aitolia,923,B-LOC,0.9871153831481934,B-LOC,0.9999901056289673,B-LOC,0.9999934434890747,B-GPE,B-GPE
730,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,188,",",930,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
731,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,189,is,932,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
732,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,190,fast,935,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
733,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,191,adding,940,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
734,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,192,the,947,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
735,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,193,island,951,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
736,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,194,of,958,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
737,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,195,Artemita,961,B-LOC,0.9908313155174255,B-LOC,0.9999881982803345,B-LOC,0.999990701675415,B-ORG,B-GPE
738,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,196,to,970,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
739,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,197,the,973,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
740,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,198,mainland,977,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
741,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,199,by,986,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
742,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,200,the,989,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
743,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,201,continual,993,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
744,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,202,deposits,1003,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
745,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,203,of,1012,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
746,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,204,earth,1015,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
747,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,205,which,1021,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
748,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,206,it,1027,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
749,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,207,brings,1030,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
750,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,208,down,1037,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
751,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,209,its,1042,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
752,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,210,stream,1046,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
753,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.2.1,211,.,1052,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
754,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,0,§,0,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
755,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,1,4.3.1,2,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,B-CARDINAL
756,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,2,AETOLIA,9,O,-,B-LOC,0.9999798536300659,B-LOC,0.9999847412109375,O,O
757,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,3,:,16,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
758,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,4,The,18,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
759,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,5,peoples,22,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
760,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,6,of,30,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
761,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,7,Aitolia,33,B-LOC,0.8254609107971191,B-LOC,0.9999873638153076,B-LOC,0.99998939037323,B-GPE,B-GPE
762,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,8,are,41,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
763,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,9,the,45,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
764,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,10,Athamanes,49,B-MISC,0.9755546450614929,B-MISC,0.9999755620956421,B-MISC,0.9999761581420898,O,B-NORP
765,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,11,",",58,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
766,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,12,the,60,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
767,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,13,Tymphaei,64,B-MISC,0.9394960403442383,B-MISC,0.9999586343765259,B-MISC,0.999956488609314,O,B-NORP
768,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,14,",",72,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
769,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,15,the,74,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
770,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,16,Ephyri,78,B-MISC,0.9795989990234375,B-MISC,0.9999716281890869,B-MISC,0.9999731779098511,O,B-NORP
771,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,17,",",84,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
772,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,18,the,86,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
773,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,19,Aenienses,90,B-MISC,0.9972922205924988,B-MISC,0.9999676942825317,B-MISC,0.9999738931655884,B-PERSON,B-NORP
774,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,20,",",99,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
775,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,21,the,101,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
776,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,22,Perrhaebi,105,B-MISC,0.9762570858001709,B-MISC,0.9999457597732544,B-MISC,0.9999538660049438,B-PERSON,B-NORP
777,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,23,",",114,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
778,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,24,the,116,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
779,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,25,Dolopes,120,B-MISC,0.991078794002533,B-MISC,0.9999213218688965,B-MISC,0.9999395608901978,O,B-NORP
780,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,26,",",127,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
781,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,27,the,129,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
782,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,28,Maraces,133,B-MISC,0.9629000425338745,B-MISC,0.9998146891593933,B-MISC,0.9998583793640137,O,B-NORP
783,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,29,",",140,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
784,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,30,and,142,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
785,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,31,the,146,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
786,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,32,Atraces,150,B-MISC,0.977891206741333,B-MISC,0.9999414682388306,B-MISC,0.9999549388885498,B-PERSON,B-NORP
787,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,33,",",157,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
788,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,34,in,159,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
789,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,35,whose,162,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
790,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,36,territory,168,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
791,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,37,rises,178,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
792,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,38,the,184,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
793,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,39,river,188,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
794,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,40,Atrax,194,B-LOC,0.9195402264595032,B-LOC,0.9999537467956543,B-LOC,0.999981164932251,B-PERSON,B-LOC
795,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,41,",",199,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
796,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,42,which,201,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
797,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,43,flows,207,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
798,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,44,into,213,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
799,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,45,the,218,O,-,O,-,O,-,B-LOC,B-LOC
800,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,46,Ionian,222,B-LOC,0.9772965312004089,B-LOC,0.9999845623970032,B-LOC,0.9999871253967285,I-LOC,I-LOC
801,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,47,Sea,229,I-LOC,0.9772965312004089,I-LOC,0.9999845623970032,I-LOC,0.9999871253967285,I-LOC,I-LOC
802,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,48,.,232,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
803,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,49,Calydon,234,B-LOC,0.9912204146385193,B-LOC,0.999992847442627,B-LOC,0.9999943971633911,B-PERSON,B-GPE
804,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,50,is,242,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
805,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,51,a,245,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
806,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,52,city,247,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
807,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,53,of,252,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
808,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,54,Aitolia,255,B-LOC,0.996632993221283,B-LOC,0.9999871253967285,B-LOC,0.9999908208847046,B-GPE,B-GPE
809,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,55,",",262,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
810,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,56,situate,264,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
811,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,57,at,272,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
812,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,58,a,275,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
813,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,59,distance,277,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
814,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,60,of,286,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
815,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,61,seven,289,O,-,O,-,O,-,B-QUANTITY,B-QUANTITY
816,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,62,miles,295,O,-,O,-,O,-,I-QUANTITY,I-QUANTITY
817,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,63,from,301,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
818,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,64,the,306,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
819,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,65,sea,310,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
820,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,66,",",313,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
821,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,67,and,315,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
822,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,68,near,319,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
823,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,69,the,324,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
824,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,70,banks,328,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
825,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,71,of,334,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
826,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,72,the,337,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
827,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,73,river,341,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
828,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,74,Evenus,347,B-LOC,0.9351760745048523,B-LOC,0.9999812841415405,B-LOC,0.999987006187439,B-LOC,B-LOC
829,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,75,.,353,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
830,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,76,We,355,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
831,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,77,then,358,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
832,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,78,come,363,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
833,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,79,to,368,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
834,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,80,Macynia,371,B-LOC,0.905846893787384,B-LOC,0.9999804496765137,B-LOC,0.999984860420227,B-GPE,B-GPE
835,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,81,",",378,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
836,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,82,and,380,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
837,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,83,Molycria,384,B-MISC,0.8911168575286865,B-LOC,0.9999823570251465,B-LOC,0.9999876022338867,B-PERSON,B-GPE
838,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,84,",",392,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
839,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,85,behind,394,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
840,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,86,which,401,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
841,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,87,lie,407,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
842,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,88,Mounts,411,B-LOC,0.7821256816387177,B-LOC,0.9999212622642517,B-LOC,0.9999104142189026,B-LOC,B-LOC
843,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,89,Chalcis,418,I-LOC,0.7821256816387177,I-LOC,0.9999212622642517,I-LOC,0.9999104142189026,I-LOC,I-LOC
844,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,90,and,426,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
845,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,91,Taphiassus,430,B-LOC,0.648418128490448,B-LOC,0.9999635219573975,B-LOC,0.9999817609786987,B-PERSON,B-GPE
846,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,92,.,440,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
847,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,93,On,442,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
848,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,94,the,445,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
849,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,95,coast,449,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
850,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,96,again,455,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
851,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,97,",",460,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
852,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,98,there,462,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
853,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,99,is,468,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
854,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,100,the,471,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
855,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,101,promontory,475,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
856,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,102,of,486,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
857,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,103,Antirrhium,489,B-LOC,0.9464738368988037,B-LOC,0.9999788999557495,B-LOC,0.9999912977218628,B-PERSON,B-LOC
858,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,104,",",499,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
859,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,105,off,501,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
860,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,106,which,505,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
861,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,107,is,511,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
862,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,108,the,514,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
863,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,109,mouth,518,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
864,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,110,of,524,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
865,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,111,the,527,O,-,O,-,O,-,B-LOC,B-LOC
866,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,112,Corinthian,531,B-LOC,0.9748525023460388,B-LOC,0.9999850392341614,B-LOC,0.9999855160713196,I-LOC,I-LOC
867,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,113,Gulf,542,I-LOC,0.9748525023460388,I-LOC,0.9999850392341614,I-LOC,0.9999855160713196,I-LOC,I-LOC
868,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,114,",",546,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
869,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,115,which,548,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
870,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,116,flows,554,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
871,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,117,in,560,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
872,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,118,and,563,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
873,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,119,separates,567,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
874,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,120,Aitolia,577,B-LOC,0.9421222805976868,B-LOC,0.9999910593032837,B-LOC,0.9999911785125732,B-GPE,B-GPE
875,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,121,from,585,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
876,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,122,the,590,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
877,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,123,Peloponnesus,594,B-LOC,0.9689637422561646,B-LOC,0.9999291896820068,B-LOC,0.9999819993972778,B-ORG,B-LOC
878,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,124,",",606,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
879,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,125,being,608,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
880,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,126,less,614,O,-,O,-,O,-,B-QUANTITY,O
881,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,127,than,619,O,-,O,-,O,-,I-QUANTITY,O
882,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,128,one,624,O,-,O,-,O,-,I-QUANTITY,B-QUANTITY
883,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,129,mile,628,O,-,O,-,O,-,I-QUANTITY,I-QUANTITY
884,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,130,in,633,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
885,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,131,width,636,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
886,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,132,.,641,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
887,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,133,The,643,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
888,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,134,promontory,647,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
889,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,135,which,658,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
890,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,136,faces,664,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
891,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,137,it,670,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
892,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,138,on,673,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
893,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,139,the,676,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
894,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,140,opposite,680,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
895,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,141,side,689,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
896,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,142,is,694,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
897,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,143,called,697,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
898,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,144,Rhion,704,B-LOC,0.8180840611457825,B-LOC,0.9999786615371704,B-LOC,0.9999805688858032,B-ORG,B-GPE
899,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,145,.,709,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
900,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,146,The,711,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
901,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,147,towns,715,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
902,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,148,of,721,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
903,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,149,Aitolia,724,B-LOC,0.9996325969696045,B-LOC,0.9999732971191406,B-LOC,0.9999915361404419,B-GPE,B-GPE
904,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,150,",",731,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
905,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,151,however,733,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
906,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,152,",",740,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
907,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,153,on,742,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
908,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,154,the,745,O,-,O,-,O,-,B-LOC,O
909,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,155,Corinthian,749,B-LOC,0.9244211912155151,B-LOC,0.9999836683273315,B-LOC,0.9999819397926331,I-LOC,B-LOC
910,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,156,Gulf,760,I-LOC,0.9244211912155151,I-LOC,0.9999836683273315,I-LOC,0.9999819397926331,I-LOC,I-LOC
911,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,157,are,765,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
912,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,158,Naupactus,769,B-LOC,0.6875844597816467,B-LOC,0.9998873472213745,B-LOC,0.9999688863754272,B-ORG,B-LOC
913,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,159,and,779,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
914,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,160,Pylene,783,B-LOC,0.7016496658325195,B-LOC,0.999855637550354,B-LOC,0.9999756813049316,B-ORG,B-GPE
915,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,161,;,789,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
916,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,162,and,791,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
917,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,163,",",794,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
918,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,164,more,796,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
919,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,165,inland,801,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
920,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,166,",",807,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
921,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,167,Pleuron,809,B-LOC,0.9351820349693298,B-LOC,0.9999332427978516,B-LOC,0.9999727010726929,B-GPE,B-GPE
922,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,168,and,817,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
923,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,169,Halicyrna,821,B-LOC,0.8712721467018127,B-LOC,0.9998635053634644,B-LOC,0.9999734163284302,B-GPE,B-GPE
924,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,170,.,830,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
925,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,171,The,832,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
926,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,172,most,836,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
927,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,173,famous,841,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
928,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,174,mountains,848,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
929,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,175,are,858,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
930,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,176,Tomarus,862,B-LOC,0.8938564658164978,B-LOC,0.9995936751365662,B-LOC,0.9998849630355835,B-GPE,B-LOC
931,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,177,",",869,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
932,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,178,in,871,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
933,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,179,the,874,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
934,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,180,district,878,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
935,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,181,of,887,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
936,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,182,Dodona,890,B-LOC,0.9842031002044678,B-LOC,0.9999796152114868,B-LOC,0.9999918937683105,B-GPE,B-GPE
937,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,183,",",896,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
938,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,184,Crania,898,B-LOC,0.4875868558883667,B-LOC,0.998944103717804,B-LOC,0.9997655749320984,B-PERSON,B-GPE
939,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,185,in,905,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
940,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,186,Ambracia,908,B-LOC,0.9620760083198547,B-LOC,0.9999396800994873,B-LOC,0.9999771118164062,O,B-GPE
941,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,187,",",916,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
942,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,188,Aracynthus,918,B-MISC,0.7841072082519531,B-LOC,0.9976425766944885,B-LOC,0.9996505975723267,B-NORP,B-GPE
943,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,189,in,929,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
944,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,190,Acarnania,932,B-LOC,0.9883025288581848,B-LOC,0.9999358654022217,B-LOC,0.9999772310256958,B-GPE,B-GPE
945,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,191,",",941,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
946,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,192,and,943,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
947,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,193,Acanthon,947,B-MISC,0.5802450776100159,B-LOC,0.9995049238204956,B-LOC,0.9996722936630249,O,B-GPE
948,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,194,",",955,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
949,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,195,Panaetolium,957,B-MISC,0.5822985172271729,B-LOC,0.9988100528717041,B-LOC,0.9996055960655212,B-PERSON,B-LOC
950,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,196,",",968,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
951,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,197,and,970,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
952,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,198,Macynium,974,B-MISC,0.7498387694358826,B-LOC,0.999908447265625,B-LOC,0.9998325109481812,B-PERSON,B-GPE
953,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,199,",",982,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
954,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,200,in,984,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
955,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,201,Aitolia,987,B-LOC,0.9996047616004944,B-LOC,0.9999897480010986,B-LOC,0.9999889135360718,B-GPE,B-GPE
956,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.3.1,202,.,994,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
957,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,0,§,0,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
958,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,1,4.4.1,2,O,-,O,-,O,-,B-CARDINAL,B-CARDINAL
959,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,2,LOCRIS,9,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
960,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,3,AND,16,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
961,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,4,PHOCIS,20,O,-,B-LOC,0.9999418258666992,B-LOC,0.9999240636825562,O,O
962,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,5,:,26,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
963,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,6,Next,28,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
964,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,7,to,33,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
965,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,8,Aitolia,36,B-LOC,0.9886548519134521,B-LOC,0.9999814033508301,B-LOC,0.9999889135360718,B-GPE,B-GPE
966,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,9,are,44,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
967,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,10,the,48,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
968,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,11,Locri,52,B-LOC,0.9614527821540833,B-MISC,0.9999728202819824,B-MISC,0.9999796152114868,B-PERSON,B-NORP
969,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,12,surnamed,58,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
970,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,13,Ozolae,67,B-LOC,0.6208587288856506,B-MISC,0.9999779462814331,B-MISC,0.9999843835830688,B-PERSON,B-GPE
971,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,14,;,73,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
972,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,15,a,75,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
973,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,16,people,77,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
974,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,17,exempt,84,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
975,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,18,from,91,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
976,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,19,tribute,96,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
977,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,20,.,103,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
978,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,21,Here,105,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
979,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,22,is,110,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
980,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,23,the,113,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
981,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,24,town,117,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
982,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,25,of,122,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
983,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,26,Oianthe,125,B-LOC,0.9968670010566711,B-LOC,0.9999786615371704,B-LOC,0.9999703168869019,O,B-GPE
984,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,27,",",132,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
985,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,28,the,134,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
986,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,29,port,138,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
987,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,30,of,143,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
988,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,31,Apollo,146,B-LOC,0.9551171660423279,B-LOC,0.8429955542087555,B-LOC,0.9998665452003479,B-ORG,O
989,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,32,Phaestius,153,I-LOC,0.9551171660423279,I-LOC,0.8429955542087555,I-LOC,0.9998665452003479,I-ORG,B-GPE
990,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,33,",",162,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
991,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,34,and,164,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
992,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,35,the,168,O,-,O,-,O,-,B-LOC,O
993,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,36,Gulf,172,B-LOC,0.9663518269856771,B-LOC,0.9999651511510214,B-LOC,0.9999654690424601,I-LOC,B-LOC
994,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,37,of,177,I-LOC,0.9663518269856771,I-LOC,0.9999651511510214,I-LOC,0.9999654690424601,I-LOC,O
995,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,38,Crissa,180,I-LOC,0.9663518269856771,I-LOC,0.9999651511510214,I-LOC,0.9999654690424601,I-LOC,B-LOC
996,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,39,.,186,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
997,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,40,In,188,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
998,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,41,the,191,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
999,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,42,interior,195,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1000,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,43,are,204,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1001,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,44,the,208,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1002,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,45,towns,212,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1003,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,46,of,218,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1004,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,47,Argyna,221,B-LOC,0.9951817393302917,B-LOC,0.9999454021453857,B-LOC,0.9999592304229736,B-GPE,B-GPE
1005,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,48,",",227,O,-,O,-,O,-,I-GPE,O
1006,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,49,Eupalia,229,B-LOC,0.9632202386856079,B-LOC,0.999930739402771,B-LOC,0.9999573230743408,B-PERSON,B-GPE
1007,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,50,",",236,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1008,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,51,Phaestum,238,B-LOC,0.7509961724281311,B-LOC,0.9999676942825317,B-LOC,0.9999756813049316,B-ORG,B-GPE
1009,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,52,",",246,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1010,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,53,and,248,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1011,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,54,Calamisus,252,B-MISC,0.7965716123580933,B-LOC,0.9999631643295288,B-LOC,0.9999749660491943,B-ORG,B-GPE
1012,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,55,.,261,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1013,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,56,Beyond,263,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1014,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,57,are,270,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1015,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,58,the,274,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1016,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,59,Cirrhaean,278,B-LOC,0.9157842993736267,B-MISC,0.3747420907020569,B-LOC,0.9024590849876404,B-NORP,B-NORP
1017,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,60,plains,288,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1018,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,61,of,295,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1019,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,62,Phocis,298,B-LOC,0.9984539747238159,B-LOC,0.9999771118164062,B-LOC,0.9999719858169556,B-GPE,B-GPE
1020,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,63,",",304,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1021,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,64,the,306,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1022,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,65,town,310,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1023,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,66,of,315,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1024,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,67,Cirrha,318,B-LOC,0.9994738698005676,B-LOC,0.9999922513961792,B-LOC,0.9999927282333374,B-FAC,B-GPE
1025,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,68,",",324,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1026,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,69,and,326,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1027,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,70,the,330,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1028,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,71,port,334,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1029,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,72,of,339,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1030,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,73,Chalaeon,342,B-LOC,0.9994798302650452,B-LOC,0.9999929666519165,B-LOC,0.9999938011169434,B-ORG,B-GPE
1031,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,74,",",350,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1032,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,75,seven,352,O,-,O,-,O,-,B-QUANTITY,B-QUANTITY
1033,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,76,miles,358,O,-,O,-,O,-,I-QUANTITY,I-QUANTITY
1034,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,77,from,364,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1035,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,78,which,369,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1036,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,79,",",374,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1037,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,80,in,376,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1038,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,81,the,379,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1039,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,82,interior,383,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1040,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,83,",",391,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1041,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,84,is,393,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1042,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,85,situate,396,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1043,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,86,the,404,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1044,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,87,free,408,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1045,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,88,town,413,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1046,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,89,of,418,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1047,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,90,Delphi,421,B-LOC,0.989042341709137,B-LOC,0.9999929666519165,B-LOC,0.9999942779541016,B-GPE,B-GPE
1048,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,91,",",427,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1049,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,92,at,429,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1050,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,93,the,432,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1051,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,94,foot,436,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1052,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,95,of,441,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1053,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,96,Mount,444,B-LOC,0.9786906838417053,B-LOC,0.9998806118965149,B-LOC,0.9998841881752014,B-LOC,B-LOC
1054,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,97,Parnassus,450,I-LOC,0.9786906838417053,I-LOC,0.9998806118965149,I-LOC,0.9998841881752014,I-LOC,I-LOC
1055,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,98,",",459,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1056,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,99,and,461,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1057,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,100,having,465,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1058,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,101,the,472,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1059,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,102,most,476,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1060,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,103,celebrated,481,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1061,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,104,oracle,492,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1062,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,105,of,499,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1063,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,106,Apollo,502,B-MISC,0.7235785722732544,B-PER,0.9997467398643494,B-PER,0.999573290348053,B-ORG,B-PERSON
1064,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,107,throughout,509,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1065,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,108,the,520,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1066,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,109,whole,524,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1067,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,110,world,530,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1068,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,111,.,535,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1069,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,112,There,537,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1070,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,113,is,543,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1071,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,114,the,546,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,B-FAC
1072,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,115,Fountain,550,O,-,B-LOC,0.9989047348499298,B-LOC,0.9992332756519318,O,I-FAC
1073,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,116,too,559,O,-,I-LOC,0.9989047348499298,I-LOC,0.9992332756519318,O,I-FAC
1074,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,117,of,563,O,-,I-LOC,0.9989047348499298,I-LOC,0.9992332756519318,O,I-FAC
1075,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,118,Castalia,566,B-LOC,0.9781525731086731,I-LOC,0.9989047348499298,I-LOC,0.9992332756519318,B-GPE,B-GPE
1076,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,119,",",574,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1077,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,120,and,576,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1078,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,121,the,580,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1079,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,122,river,584,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1080,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,123,Cephisus,590,O,-,B-LOC,0.9433743357658386,B-LOC,0.9915398955345154,B-ORG,B-LOC
1081,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,124,which,599,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1082,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,125,flows,605,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1083,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,126,past,611,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1084,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,127,Delphi,616,B-LOC,0.9123382568359375,B-LOC,0.9999940395355225,B-LOC,0.999994158744812,B-ORG,B-GPE
1085,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,128,",",622,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1086,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,129,rising,624,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1087,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,130,in,631,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1088,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,131,the,634,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1089,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,132,former,638,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1090,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,133,city,645,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1091,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,134,of,650,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1092,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,135,Lilaea,653,B-LOC,0.99818354845047,B-LOC,0.9999821186065674,B-LOC,0.999985933303833,B-PERSON,B-GPE
1093,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,136,.,659,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1094,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,137,Besides,661,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1095,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,138,these,669,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1096,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,139,",",674,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1097,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,140,there,676,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1098,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,141,is,682,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1099,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,142,the,685,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1100,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,143,town,689,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1101,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,144,of,694,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1102,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,145,Crissa,697,B-LOC,0.9909687638282776,B-LOC,0.9999685287475586,B-LOC,0.9999725818634033,B-PERSON,B-GPE
1103,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,146,and,704,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1104,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,147,that,708,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1105,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,148,of,713,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1106,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,149,Anticyra,716,B-LOC,0.9907644987106323,B-LOC,0.9999505281448364,B-LOC,0.9999678134918213,B-PERSON,B-GPE
1107,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,150,",",724,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1108,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,151,with,726,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1109,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,152,the,731,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1110,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,153,Bulenses,735,B-MISC,0.8986944556236267,B-MISC,0.9998350143432617,B-MISC,0.9999154806137085,B-ORG,B-NORP
1111,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,154,;,743,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1112,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,155,as,745,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1113,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,156,also,748,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1114,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,157,Naulochum,753,B-LOC,0.9420896172523499,B-LOC,0.9998822212219238,B-LOC,0.999951958656311,B-PERSON,B-GPE
1115,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,158,",",762,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1116,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,159,Pyrrha,764,B-LOC,0.8881632685661316,B-LOC,0.9999158382415771,B-LOC,0.9999606609344482,B-ORG,B-GPE
1117,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,160,",",770,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1118,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,161,Amphissa,772,B-MISC,0.7765728831291199,B-LOC,0.9999251365661621,B-LOC,0.999967098236084,B-GPE,B-GPE
1119,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,162,",",780,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1120,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,163,exempt,782,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1121,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,164,from,789,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1122,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,165,all,794,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1123,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,166,tribute,798,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1124,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,167,",",805,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1125,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,168,Tithrone,807,B-MISC,0.8764094114303589,B-LOC,0.9998434782028198,B-LOC,0.9999558925628662,B-PERSON,B-GPE
1126,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,169,",",815,O,-,O,-,O,-,I-PERSON,O
1127,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,170,Tritea,817,B-MISC,0.888303816318512,B-LOC,0.9998698234558105,B-LOC,0.9999663829803467,O,B-GPE
1128,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,171,",",823,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1129,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,172,Ambrysus,825,B-MISC,0.9689447283744812,B-LOC,0.9998968839645386,B-LOC,0.9999665021896362,B-ORG,B-GPE
1130,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,173,",",833,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1131,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,174,and,835,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1132,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,175,Drymaea,839,B-MISC,0.9586963057518005,B-LOC,0.9998942613601685,B-LOC,0.9999639987945557,B-PERSON,B-GPE
1133,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,176,",",846,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1134,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,177,which,848,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1135,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,178,district,854,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1136,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,179,has,863,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1137,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,180,also,867,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1138,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,181,the,872,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1139,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,182,name,876,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1140,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,183,of,881,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1141,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,184,Daulis,884,B-LOC,0.7131026983261108,B-LOC,0.9999630451202393,B-LOC,0.999966025352478,B-GPE,B-GPE
1142,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,185,.,890,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1143,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,186,The,892,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1144,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,187,extremity,896,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1145,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,188,of,906,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1146,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,189,the,909,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1147,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,190,gulf,913,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1148,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,191,washes,918,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1149,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,192,one,925,O,-,O,-,O,-,B-CARDINAL,B-CARDINAL
1150,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,193,corner,929,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1151,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,194,of,936,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1152,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,195,Boeotia,939,B-LOC,0.9989480376243591,B-LOC,0.9999887943267822,B-LOC,0.9999911785125732,B-GPE,B-GPE
1153,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,196,",",946,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1154,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,197,with,948,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1155,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,198,its,953,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1156,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,199,towns,957,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1157,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,200,of,963,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1158,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,201,Siphae,966,B-LOC,0.9943769574165344,B-LOC,0.9999700784683228,B-LOC,0.9999785423278809,B-GPE,B-GPE
1159,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,202,and,973,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1160,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,203,Thebes,977,B-LOC,0.9872995018959045,B-LOC,0.9999725818634033,B-LOC,0.9999793767929077,B-GPE,B-GPE
1161,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,204,",",983,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1162,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,205,surnamed,985,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1163,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,206,the,994,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1164,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,207,Corsian,998,B-MISC,0.967106819152832,B-MISC,0.9999881982803345,B-MISC,0.9999847412109375,B-NORP,B-NORP
1165,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,208,",",1005,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1166,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,209,in,1007,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1167,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,210,the,1010,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1168,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,211,vicinity,1014,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1169,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,212,of,1023,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1170,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,213,Helicon,1026,B-LOC,0.8761523962020874,B-LOC,0.9999698400497437,B-LOC,0.99997878074646,B-LOC,B-GPE
1171,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,214,.,1033,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1172,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,215,The,1035,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1173,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,216,third,1039,O,-,O,-,O,-,B-ORDINAL,B-ORDINAL
1174,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,217,town,1045,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1175,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,218,of,1050,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1176,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,219,Boeotia,1053,B-LOC,0.9980698227882385,B-LOC,0.9999890327453613,B-LOC,0.9999924898147583,B-GPE,B-GPE
1177,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,220,on,1061,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1178,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,221,this,1064,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
1179,urn:cts:latinLit:phi0978.phi001:4.4.1,222,sea,1069,O,-,O,-,O,-,O,O
